jewcy.com 2007-10-24

# Privacy Policy | Jewcy.com

**Jewcy Partners, LLC Privacy Policy**  
Jewcy Partners, LLC has a strong commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: Jewcy.com.  
 **  
User Information Collected on Our Site**  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.

**Security**  
This site has standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Jewcy takes standard precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use commercially reasonable measures (and not necessarily the latest or most advanced technology) to protect member information that is stored within our database. Jewcy does not guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. For any additional information about the security measures we use on Jewcy, please contact us at [info@jewcy.com](mailto:info@jewcy.com).

**Registered Users**  
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (name and email address) if they wish to post messages in our forums, post events and set up user profiles. We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user registration notification and password reset emails.

**Email Choice/Opt-out**  
Members may opt out of receiving updates, newsletters, communication or notifications at any time by emailing [info@jewcy.com](mailto:info@jewcy.com) or responding to emails from Jewcy with notification that they want to unsubscribe.

**Third Party Privacy Policies**  
This site contains links to other sites. Jewcy is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. When linking to another site, a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on Jewcy.

**Public Disclosure of Personal Information  
** Jewcy members can create their profiles, and have the ability to change their profile information at any time. They also have the ability to control how the service communicates with them. This site makes forums and other ways to interact with users available to its members. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. Jewcy collects information submitted by its users and other profile data, including but not limited to, personal interests, gender, age, education and occupation, in order to assist users to find and communicate with each other. Jewcy users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account. Jewcy has no knowledge or control over how such profile or personal information may be used by others. 

User Profile information including members' pictures and chosen screen names are displayed to users and visitors in order to facilitate interaction. Email addresses are used for the purposes of sending notifications related to the service. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's personal network. Users within a personal network communicate on Jewcy with each other through the Jewcy service, without disclosing their email addresses – unless they so chose. Users' full names are never directly revealed by Jewcy to other members or visitors. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, Jewcy allows users to search for other members using keyword or geographic location. We may also use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service.

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, Jewcy will not knowingly disclose personal information to any third-party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the Jewcy Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety, security and livelihood of members of the public and users of the service. Jewcy reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of Jewcy or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below.  
 **  
Changes in Our Privacy Policy**  
From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of the changes. 

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at [info@jewcy.com](mailto:info@jewcy.com).
